

Falmouth, Cornwall, United Kingdom

### **Summary**

I am an avid programmer with a strong knowledge of version control using Git, experience with multiple programming languages and an excitement for facing new, interesting challenges. I have become a confident presenter who is comfortable with all aspects of teamwork, including leading a team and liaising between different disciplines on a team. My ideal position would be progressing to a senior programmer or as a project manager, and as such I am very interested in opportunities to grow towards these roles.

### Skills\_\_\_\_

- Languages: C#, C++
- · Game Engines: Unity, Unreal Engine 4
- Version Control: Git
- · Project Management: Agile, scrum, sprint planning

### Published Games

#### Yvaga Station - Team Leader

Unity 2018.4

May 2020

- SELF PUBLISHED TO ITCH.IO (HTTPS://DAYLUKE.ITCH.IO/YVAGA-STATION)
- · Developed and implemented in Unity 2018.4
- Presented a concept pitch to in order to continue development past prototype stage
- Implemented symmetric multiplayer game using PUN2 for networking
- Designed and implemented a modular custom movement system to expand on the options available to the player
- The game has 192 downloads (as of September 2020) on itch.io

## **Programming Projects**

Snake C++ OpenGL

#### HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/HDONOVAN96/SNAKE

- Developed and implemented in OpenGL for C++
- Programmed a game of snake including collision detection and random 'apple' placement
- · Displays players score upon death without the use of text as a challenge to see if the information could still be conveyed clearly
- Set up initial conditions so the game could be restarted with a single key press

### Education

#### **Falmouth University**

Falmouth, United Kingdom

BSc Computing For Games

Sept. 2019 - Current

- · Worked with a multi-discipline team to bring several games through a full development cycle
- · Learned about and improved upon creating neat, maintainable code through commenting and UML diagrams
- Participated in modules including creating a custom physical controller and designing an audio generation tool
- · Received and responded to feedback from concept pitches, module evaluations and regular game progress reviews
- · I am involved with a peer-assisted learning programme designed to help teach new students vital problem solving skills
- · I am also active with helping other students with general, programming, and version control questions outside of this role

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

#### Senior Ambassador Falmouth, Cornwall

**FXPLUS** 

**FXPLUS** 

June 2020 - Current

- Increased responsibility for the smooth running of events
- Manages the distribution of Student Ambassadors during events
- Relied on to handle any complications or problems that arise during an event

#### **Student Ambassador**

Falmouth, Cornwall

October 2019 - June 2020

• Involved in the running of university events and open days

- · This includes discussing the course with potential students and leading group tours around the campus
- I have also spoken on an online Q&A panel as part of this role

SEPTEMBER 22, 2020 HARRY DONOVAN · RÉSUMÉ